Finding Aid for the ABC Television Network Scripts and Production Files PASC.0220
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3. Scripts and Production files, Late 1950s, late 1960s and 1973; (Boxes 10-15)
  - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - annotated script, 11 Oct 1968 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - production information, 1968-69 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Mr. Deeds Goes to Town - script, 11 Mar 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - New People (The)
    - New People (The) - production information, broadcast standards, and outline, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - New People (The) - annotated script, 27 Nov 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Writers: Serling, Rod
    - New People (The) - incomplete script, no date (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - New People (The) - outline, 24 Feb 1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Writers: Spelling, Aaron; Gordon, Larry; Serling, Rod
    - New People (The) - script, 11 Nov 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Shadow Man
    - Shadow Man - annotated script, no date (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Writers: Soderberg, Robert
    - Shadow Man - annotated script, 25 Sep 1968 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Shadow Man - annotated script, production information, broadcast standards, and notes, Aug 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Shadow Man - outline, 18 Mar 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Streets of San Francisco (The)
    - Blockade - production information, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Blockade - script, 1 Oct 1973 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Writers: Menzies, James; Spies, Adrian
    - Chapel of the Damned - Productions information, annotated synopsis, cast list, and shooting schedule, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Chapel of the Damned - script, 26 Oct 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Writers: Schlitt, Robert
    - Commitment - production information), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Commitment - script, 9 Oct 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Writers: Black, John D. F.
    - Commitment - script, 9 Oct 1973 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Crossfire - annotated script, 12 Jul 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Writers: McNeely, Jerry
    - Crossfire - annotated script, 12 Jul 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Crossfire - production information and annotated outline, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Death and the Favored Few - Productions information, annotated synopsis, cast list, and shooting schedule, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Death and the Favored Few - script, 5 Dec 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Writers: Coon, Gene L.
    - Hard Breed (The) - annotated script, 22 Oct 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Writers: Byrnes, Jim; Bishop, Ron
    - Hard Breed (The) - annotated script, 26 Oct 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Hard Breed (The) - production information, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Inferno - productions information, cast list, and shooting schedule, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Inferno - script, 14 Nov 1973 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Writers: Miller, James M.
    - Rampage - Productions information, annotated synopsis, cast list, and shooting schedule, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Rampage - script, 6 Dec 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Writers: Ruben, Albert
    - Rampage - script, 6 Dec 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - String of Puppets, A - productioniinformation, annotated synopsis, cast list, and shooting schedule, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - String of Puppets, A - script, 15 Nov 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Writers: Weingart, Mark; Schmerer, James
    - Thirty Year Pin (The) - script, 6 Jun 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Writers: Lewin, Robert
  - Under the Yum Yum Tree
    - Hang Up (The) - annotated pilot script, 19 Sep 1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Hang Up (The) - annotated pilot script, 19 Sep 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Hang Up (The) - annotated pilot script, 23 Aug 1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Hang Up (The) - annotated pilot script, 19 Sep 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Hang Up (The) - annotated pilot script, 19 Sep 1968 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Hang Up (The) - annotated pilot script, 19 Sep 1968 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Hang Up (The) - Pilot script, 23 Aug 1968 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Hang Up (The) - Pilot script, 19 Sep 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Production file - productioniinformation, and broadcast standards, 1968-69 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Young Lawyers (The)
    - Young Lawyers (The) - annotated script, 20 Feb 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Writers: Zagor, Michael
    - Young Lawyers (The) - outline, no date (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Young Lawyers (The) - productioniinformation, broadcast standards, and script pages, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Series 4. Walt Disney Productions, Late 1950s; (Boxes 1-6)
  The Walt Disney Productions series appear to have been generated by Walt Disney Productions and copied to the network. It is not clear what office at ABC (if any) these files came from. They form a self-contained unit of materials exclusively associated with Disney television productions, which happen to have aired on ABC. The bulk of the series contains scripts and a small amount of production information. The series is arranged by project title.